[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What European island is partially occupied by a neighbouring island nation, which has led to centuries of dispute?", "correct_answer": "Ireland", "incorrect_answers": ["Sardinia", "Sicily", "Iceland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The turquoise and poinsettia are symbols of this winter month.", "correct_answer": "December", "incorrect_answers": ["January", "February", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who wrote the first textbook on Geometry?", "correct_answer": "Euclid", "incorrect_answers": ["Thales", "Archimedes", "Van Nostrand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the role of Tommy in the 1975 movie Tommy\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Roger Daltrey", "incorrect_answers": ["Eric Clapton", "Elton John", "Keith Moon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which sizes are for those who are 5 2 - 5 3 tall, with a lower bust and a shorter back?", "correct_answer": "Half sizes", "incorrect_answers": ["Miss Petite", "Junior Petite", "Misses sizes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following metropolitan areas is the largest in terms of population?", "correct_answer": "New York City", "incorrect_answers": ["London", "Paris", "Los Angeles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the western movie High Noon released?", "correct_answer": "1952", "incorrect_answers": ["1939", "1959", "1942"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what color does the Pekingese dog breed come?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Light gold", "White", "Black"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What characters do Haley Joel Osment and Jude Law play in the 2001 sci-fi flick, A.I.: Artificial Intelligence?", "correct_answer": "A robot and a robot", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "A human and a robot", "A human and a human"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which U.S. city is the Blackjack Hall of Fame located?", "correct_answer": "San Diego", "incorrect_answers": ["New York", "Los Angeles", "Las Vegas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "China is the most populous nation in the world. India is second, and the USA is third. What is the fourth most populous nation in the world?", "correct_answer": "Indonesia", "incorrect_answers": ["Russia", "Japan", "Pakistan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In September 2008 a new, very large prime number was found. Approximately how many digits does it have?", "correct_answer": "Over 10,000", "incorrect_answers": ["Between 6,00 and 8,000", "Between 5000 and 6000", "Between 8,00 and 10,000"]}]